# **Erol Bicer**Nuclear Engineer



- **\** +82-10-7497-0705
- ✓ erolbicer@live.com
- Seoul, South Korea
- **1989.09.29**
- in LinkedIn
- R<sup>G</sup> ResearchGate

## **LANGUAGES**

| English<br>Turkish | • • • • • |  |
|--------------------|-----------|--|
|                    | • • • • • |  |
| Korean             | • • • • • |  |

# **NUCLEAR TH SYSTEM CODES**

| RELAP5  | • • • • • |  |
|---------|-----------|--|
| SNAP    | • • • • • |  |
| GOTHIC  | • • • • • |  |
| MARS-KS | • • • • • |  |
| SPACE   | • • • • • |  |
| CAP     | • • • • • |  |
|         |           |  |

# **CFD CODES**

| OpenFOAM | • • • • • |
|----------|-----------|
| CUPID    | • • • • • |

#### PROGRAMMING CODES

| PROGRAMMING CODES |           |
|-------------------|-----------|
| MATLAB            | • • • • • |
| FORTRAN           | • • • • • |
| C++               | • • • • • |
|                   |           |

# **GENERAL SOFTWARE**

| DOS       | IIX CATIA |
|-----------|-----------|
| OriginLab | ParaView  |
| MS Office | Mathcad   |

#### **PROFILE**

Throughout my academic and professional career, I have focused on nuclear safety analyses at the plant, system, and component levels utilizing system safety analysis and computational fluid dynamics codes. I have experience with various baseload nuclear power plant technologies as well as small, and micro modular reactors.

#### **EDUCATION**

**Nuclear Engineering, Ph.D.,** Seoul National University 

2017 – present | Seoul, South Korea

Nuclear Power Plant Engineering, M.Sc., KINGS ☑ 2014 – 2016 | Ulsan, South Korea

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

**Associate Manager,** FNC Technology Co., Ltd. ☑ 2016 – present | Suwon, South Korea

**R&D Engineer,** Bil-Plas Industry and Trade Co., Ltd. ☑ 2013 – 2014 | Ankara, Turkey

#### **CERTIFICATES**

**Modelling and Computation of Multiphase Flows** 

Swiss Federal Institute of Technology (ETH)

International Marketing, Business Knowledge and Intelligence
Ankara Chamber of Commerce (ATO)

## **AWARDS**

International Atomic Energy Agency Fellowship, IAEA

Full Academic Scholarship, KINGS

## **MAIN PROJECTS**

[PCCS] Conceptual Design and Development of Passive Containment Cooling System for APR1400

[SMART] System-Integrated Modular Advanced Reactor Passive Containment Cooling System

[SMR] Small and Micro Modular Reactors Technology Analyses

[PGSFR] Prototype Gen-IV Sodium-Cooled Fast Reactor Condition Analysis Project

[PAFS] Passive Auxiliary Feedwater System Development

[ATLAS] Determination of ATLAS Heat Loss and Improvement of MARS Input Model

[EUR] APR1000 PAFS Standard Design Development and EUR Certification Support

More information can be found here

# **PERSONAL VENTURES**

Nuclear Industry Association of Turkey, Board of Directors ☑

Turkish Chamber of Commerce in Korea, Co-Founder ☑

Liviboard, Co-Founder

Hacettepe Rugby Club, Founder 🖸